Aleksander Fret

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aleksander-fret

GitHub: www.github.com/alemikolo portfolio: www.aleksander.fret.com.pl

e-mail: aleksander.fret@op.pl

tel.: 605 768 401



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Web Developer Experience in developing websites with technologies: HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, PHP,

ability to design user interfaces (interest in UI UX, considerable

experience in fhe field of graphics),

currently further development in the direction of creating web

applications (React, Angular, Symfony).

Cartographer and Graphic Designer

Big experience in making various maps,

extensive editorial practice - designing of publications, DTP,

broad qualifications in the field of graphics software.

EXPERIENCE

Udacity 11.2017–08.2018 (course): www.pixel-art-maker.fret.com.pl,

www.memorygame.fret.com.pl, www.arcadegame.fret.com.pl,

www.amusementparks.fret.com.pl.

Eko-Graf 10.2008–now: Cartographer – Map Editor. Duties: designing

of graphic layouts and covers, editorial and cartographic tasks, DTP, creating of advertising materials, preparing for printing.

Personal project Under construction: developing web application (Symfony)

concerning my own version of *Talisman* board game.

WilMat 10.2016: www.wilmat.com.pl.

Emilia Fret 07.2015: www.psychoterapia.fret.com.pl.

Ewa Fret 01.2015: www.ewa.fret.com.pl.

Via Mercatorum 11.2012: www.warsztatyprzyrodnicze.com, logo, press

advertisement, advertising leaflet.

Others 04.2007–07.2008: SeaStar, Cartographer,

11.2005–12.2006: Nowa Era, Author: *Statistical tables*, 09.2004–03.2005: Wydawnictwo Marek Rożak, Cartographer.

EDUCATION

Udacity 11.2017–08.2018: Google Front-End Web Developer

Nanodegree Scholarship

Certain courses and trainings

React 16 – the complete guide (now); Angular 6 – the complete guide (now); PHP – developing CMS; PHP, MySOL, JS.

University of Wroclaw 10.1999–07.2005: bachelor's degree in *Geography*, master's degree in *Geography*, specialization in *Cartography*.

Programming

QUALIFICATIONS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, RWD, JavaScript, ES6, Jquery, React, Redux, PHP, Symfony, MySQL, Twig, Gulp, Git.

Graphics software

CorelDRAW, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Photo-Paint.

Others

English language (b1), Global Mapper.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Award in the competition organized by Ministry of Transport and Construction for master thesis *Atlas regionalny województwa łódzkiego*.

III prize for "[...] modern editorial style, usability [...]", Wrocław – przewodnik (J. Czerwiński, Eko-Graf), XX Ogólnopolski Przegląd Książki Krajoznawczo-Turystycznej. Scope of work: graphic design and creation, DTP.

PERSONAL TRAITS

Creative, with attention to detail, reliable, responsible, strongly involved.

INTERESTS

Playing the guitar, listening to the music, board games, fantasy literature, games and films, football, mountain hiking, listening to the Trojka radio channel.

I hereby give consent for my personal data to be processed for the purposes of recruitment, in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act dated 29.08.1997 (uniform text: Journal of Laws of the Republic of Poland 2002 No 101, item 926 with further amendments).